oshatrain.org 2017-02-18

# Privacy Policy - OSHAcademy

Privacy Policy

### INTRODUCTION

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Geigle Safety Group (geiglesafety.com) and our family of divisions, OSHAcademy (oshatrain.org) and Quality Safety Training (qualitysafetytraining.com). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by these web sites. This policy will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.

We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order, submit transcripts, or inform your employer of your training status.

### YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OF YOUR INFORMATION

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
    * We do require verification before making a formal name change. This helps ensure the documents produced by our websites are accurate.
  * Request us to delete any inaccurate information we have about you.
  * Request a release of your student transcript to a university or employer
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### SECURITY

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as transaction data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the web page address.

We do not collect or store any credit card data locally on our computer systems or in paper form. All credit card data collected over the phone is stored in an encrypted form by our credit card processor.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### REGISTRATION

In order to use some functions of our website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration, a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. We also require address information for shipping and to help confirm your identity when you contact us.

### ORDERS

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information, such as name and shipping address. You will also be asked for financial information, such as credit card number, expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders. We also use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

### COOKIES

We use "cookies" on our sites. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive. We use cookies to help us improve your access to our site, e.g. allowing you to login once and access multiple pages. The cookies we use are destroyed (deleted) when your browser session has ended. We do not store any long term cookies on your computer.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, google and advertisers). We use google analytics, remarketing features, and advertising reporting features to learn how vistors use our website and what their general interests are. This allows us to improve our site content to meet the needs of our customers.

[Click here to learn how to opt-out of google analytics cookie tracking.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

### LINKS

This web site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of any site that collects personally identifiable information.

### SURVEYS & CONTESTS

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you may choose whether or not to participate and disclose this information.

Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

Survey information may be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### UPDATES

Geigle Safety Group reserves the right to modify these Privacy Policies at any time without advance notice. Any changes to these Privacy Policies will be effective immediately upon posting on this page, with an updated effective date. By accessing this site after any changes have been made, you signify your agreement on a prospective basis to the modified Privacy Policy and all of the changes. Be sure to return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of these Privacy Policies.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 971-217-8721 or by email at [instructor@oshatrain.org](mailto:instructor@oshatrain.org).

**Effective Date:** September 1st, 2014.

**Last Updated:** February 5th, 2016.
